<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KMD2PDF on jiahao.blog</title><link>/tags/kmd2pdf/</link><description>Recent content in KMD2PDF on jiahao.blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/kmd2pdf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Applications of Kotlin's delegate properties</title><link>/post/kotlin-delegate-properties/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/kotlin-delegate-properties/</guid><description>Announcement time! After a long hiatus from kMD2PDF, I revved up my engines and began to work on my latest planned feature for the project&amp;hellip;
YAML support!
Yes, now YAML is in the works and you can now control basic attributes of your exported document using only front matter YAML.
This is an incredibly big milestone as this allows anyone to quickly customise their document without having to write a single line of Kotlin, and with another planned release to create a GUI exporter for markdown documents, this would greatly streamline users&amp;rsquo; experience.</description></item><item><title>Porting to FlexMark</title><link>/post/porting-flexmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/porting-flexmark/</guid><description>kMD2PDF now finally uses FlexMark as the back end for the markdown to html conversion. This is a big moment as now a lot more flexibility has been introduced for the library and that means more features.
Following my promise of making smaller and more frequent release updates, this port has ushered in version 0.2.1 of kMD2PDF and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited!
Changelog Backend library using flexmark Unit testing framework set up for testing node rendering Task list items now supported Original design Originally, the library used commonmark to handle .</description></item><item><title>Lessons on software release</title><link>/post/lessons-on-software-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/lessons-on-software-release/</guid><description>Oh boy, I screwed up bad, like really badly. Ok ok, let&amp;rsquo;s go back and see where it all began. I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt countless lessons from this and I hope you (reader) will too if you&amp;rsquo;re developing your own software.
Story time! 2 months ago, I embarked on a journey to write a markdown to PDF converter, called kMD2PDF. The initial architecture was developed such that:
.md file -&amp;gt; .html file + .</description></item></channel></rss>