<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reflection on jiahao.blog</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/tags/reflection/</link><description>Recent content in Reflection on jiahao.blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.woojiahao.com/tags/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Preparing for Technical Interviews</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/technical-interview-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/technical-interview-systems/</guid><description>My friend, Devansh, recently wrote an article about &amp;ldquo;Debunking Myths Regarding Tech Internship Applications&amp;rdquo; , and I agree with many of his points. Proofreading his article gave me the opportunity to reflect on my own personal journey through internship hunting and technical interviews in summer 2024 and I would love to share more about the systems and techniques I had used to prepare for my technical interviews.
⚠️ DISCLAIMER ⚠️</description></item><item><title>Where Have I Been? (2024 Edition)</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/where-have-i-been/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/where-have-i-been/</guid><description>I have not been posting a lot on this blog for quite a while now. This is not because I have stopped being interested in writing. Quite the opposite actually. I have been working with other companies like BetterStack and CodeCrafter&amp;rsquo;s OSS History to create articles for them.
I have also been working on several big projects like my Technical Interview Study Guide and Omashu.
I have several articles in mind that I would like to post on this blog so stay tuned!</description></item><item><title>The truth behind software projects</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/software-projects-truth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/software-projects-truth/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s 3am. You are one commit away from launching your first release of your latest idea. It&amp;rsquo;s an AI system to help people recommend names for their pets through pictures (clearly, Spot isn&amp;rsquo;t a great name). You take a swig of coffee. You fix the bug that has been sitting on the top of your Trello board for days now. git add . &amp;amp;&amp;amp; git commit -am &amp;quot;Fix issue where AI takes over the world&amp;quot; and you are off.</description></item><item><title>Porting to FlexMark</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/porting-flexmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/porting-flexmark/</guid><description>kMD2PDF now finally uses FlexMark as the back end for the markdown to html conversion. This is a big moment as now a lot more flexibility has been introduced for the library and that means more features.
Following my promise of making smaller and more frequent release updates, this port has ushered in version 0.2.1 of kMD2PDF and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited!
Changelog Backend library using flexmark Unit testing framework set up for testing node rendering Task list items now supported Original design Originally, the library used commonmark to handle .</description></item><item><title>Lessons on software release</title><link>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/lessons-on-software-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woojiahao.com/post/lessons-on-software-release/</guid><description>Oh boy, I screwed up bad, like really badly. Ok ok, let&amp;rsquo;s go back and see where it all began. I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt countless lessons from this and I hope you (reader) will too if you&amp;rsquo;re developing your own software.
Story time! 2 months ago, I embarked on a journey to write a markdown to PDF converter, called kMD2PDF. The initial architecture was developed such that:
.md file -&amp;gt; .html file + .</description></item></channel></rss>